<DialogueTree>
    <NameField>Rover</NameField>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Start</Name>
        <EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>TRAPPIST-1b is the closest planet to the star TRAPPIST-1.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <RevealFacts>
            <FactID>B_ROVER</FactID>
        </RevealFacts>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Overview</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Overview</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Atmosphere</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Atmosphere</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Lava</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Lava</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>[Exit]</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Exit</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Overview</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>TRAPPIST-1b is a terrestrial planet orbiting extremely close to TRAPPIST-1, about 1% of Earth's orbital distance.</Page>
            <Page>It is tidally locked to TRAPPIST-1, with one side always bright and the other always dark.</Page>
            <Page>It receives 4 times the amount of light as Earth, putting it well outside the habitable zone.</Page>
            <Page>Due to it's low density, it's likely covered by an enormous amount of water, most likely as vapor.</Page>
            <Page>It probably has a massive incredibly thick greenhouse atmosphere, much larger and hotter than that of Venus.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Back</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Start</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Atmosphere</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>TRAPPIST-1b is likely to have a thick greenhouse atmosphere, possibly even thicker than Venus's, heating the surface to well over 1500 kelvin.</Page>
            <Page>Due to the planet's low density, a mostly water vapor atmosphere is likely, although a carbon dioxide or pure oxygen atmosphere has not been ruled out.</Page>
            <Page>A Venus-like CO2 atmosphere could be over 30 km tall, in comparison to Venus's 16 km, and a water vapor atmosphere would have to be even larger, over 100 km tall.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Back</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Start</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Lava</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>All terrestrial planets start there lives completely covered in a global magma ocean, and TRAPPIST-1b is no exception.</Page>
            <Page>They usually cool off and solidify after some time, but due to its extreme surface temperature, planet b may have retained its magma ocean into the modern day.</Page>
        </Dialogue>
        <DialogueOptionsList>
            <DialogueOption>
                <Text>Back</Text>
                <DialogueTarget>Start</DialogueTarget>
            </DialogueOption>
        </DialogueOptionsList>
    </DialogueNode>

    <DialogueNode>
        <Name>Exit</Name>
        <Dialogue>
            <Page>...</Page>
        </Dialogue>
    </DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>